(This drama is related to specific characters, institutions, and groups It has nothing to do with the case and is purely fictitious (I hereby inform you)
(本剧与特定人物 机构 团体 案件无关 纯属虚构 特此告知)
(Seasoning, sesame oil, chili powder)
(调味料 香油 辣椒粉)
I need someone to follow a guy.
我需要派人去跟踪一个家伙
who do you want to follow
你要跟踪谁
Although Douxue will take action against gangsters
斗学虽然会对流氓动手
But he won't bully innocent people
但他不会欺负无辜的人
His name is…
他的名字是…
Li Douxue
李斗学
Usually stalking someone…
通常跟踪某人…
All for some purpose
都是为了某种目的
If you tell me your purpose first
如果你先告诉我你的目的
things might go more smoothly
事情可能会进行得更顺利
(Episode 7) You said you have the right to stay in Mingdangdong Dogeng
(第7集) 你说名堂洞都更的入住权
Are there 100 places?
有100个名额吗
It's true
是真的啦
I heard that the occupancy rights are 20 square meters.
听说20坪的入住权
Previously it cost less than 3 million won can buy it
之前用不到300万韩元的价格 就能买下
Now it has risen to 40 to 50 million won.
现在已经涨到四五千万韩元了
Oh my god
天啊
first time i saw A place where the price is so ridiculously high
我第一次看到 涨得这么离谱的地方
What right of occupancy?
什么入住权
This is not an ordinary apartment building right of occupancy
这不是一般公寓大厦的入住权
It is the right to occupy the apartment released during the city update.
是都更时释出的公寓入住权
I heard the competition is very fierce
听说竞争非常激烈
Whether it is Cheong Wa Dae or relevant government departments, Those guys from the city government
无论是青瓦台 相关政府部门 还是市政府的那群家伙
All before the news comes out
全都在都更消息出来以前
Just mobilize all your relatives I'm snapping up the land over there.
就动员所有亲戚 抢购那边的土地了
So how is the intelligence possible? Has it reached us?
所以情报怎么可能 传到我们这里呢
It's just like war
简直就跟战争没两样
Take good care and don't let the deadbeat come back.
好好守着 不要让钉子户回来
It must never happen again The bloody conflict just now
绝对不能再发生 刚刚那样的流血冲突
Yes eldest brother
是 大哥
I'll come to hand over my shift tomorrow
我明天会来交班
Thank you for your hard work
辛苦了
Brother, please come quickly
大哥 要快点来喔
Got it, brat
知道啦 臭小子
Thank you for taking charge of this big case.
负责这个大案子 真是辛苦你了
Take one portion and treat the brothers to barbecue
一份拿去请兄弟们吃烤肉
Just use the other one where needed.
另一份你就用在需要的地方吧
Hey what are you looking at
喂 你在看什么
Brother, these are really just enough to buy barbecue.
大哥 这些真的只够买烤肉耶
The brothers were injured and paid for medical expenses
兄弟们受伤看医生的医药费
It costs a lot of money…
要花不少钱…
If I make enough How can I only share the money with you?
要是我赚得够多 怎么可能只分你们这些钱呢
What's wrong...
怎么了…
Boy, I'm serious
小子 我是说真的
Am I going to give you your hard-earned money? Do you swallow it yourself?
难道我会把你们的血汗钱 自己私吞下来吗
Everything must be accumulated slowly
凡事都得慢慢累积
If we can continue to take their cases
如果我们能继续接他们的案子
I will definitely do it then I'll give you a generous bonus, okay?
到时我一定会 给你们丰厚的奖金 好吗
It's time for me to go
我该走了
Jisoo, someone is vomiting in the toilet.
吉洙 有人在厕所呕吐
Go and clear it quickly
快点去清一清
So dirty
脏死了
Yes, brother, I will handle it right away
是的 大哥 我马上处理
Brother, walk slowly
大哥慢走
How much does he give
他给多少
Two hundred for brothers, one hundred for me
兄弟们两百 我一百
is he kidding
他在开玩笑吗
The brothers’ medical expenses alone cost two hundred.
光是兄弟们的医药费就要两百了
Damn you guy, this is too much.
天杀的家伙 太过分了吧
Go to the baseball stadium and sell tickets to scalpers. I make about the same amount of money as this
去棒球场卖黄牛票 赚得也跟这差不多
Bro, give these to the brothers.
哥 把这些分给兄弟们吧
I know
我知道了
What about us?
那我们呢
Don’t we get a monthly salary?
我们不是有领月薪吗
But…
但是…
Yeah, forget it if I can't subsidize it.
是啊 我没能力补贴就算了
At least we can't drain our brothers dry.
至少不能把兄弟们榨干啊
Brother, I brought people here
大哥 我把人带来了
let her in
让她进来
welcome you
欢迎你
(Lee Yunae)
(李允爱)
We suddenly came to you. Did it scare you?
我们突然找你来 吓到你了吧
Brother, did he tell you to remit money?
大哥有吩咐你要汇款吧
How much does he want you to wire?
他要你汇多少钱
If the boss knew I told him...
要是老板知道我说出去…
I will really die miserably
我真的会死得很惨
Don't worry, we will keep it secret
你不用担心 我们一定会保密
How much does he want you to wire?
他要你汇多少钱
50 million won
五千万韩元
Fifty million won?
五千万韩元吗
Brother Guangzhuo really called you Do you want to remit 50 million won?
光卓哥真的叫你 汇五千万韩元吗
Yes it's true
对 是真的
Five checks for 10 million won in total
一千万韩元的支票 一共五张
He also said that a man should be loyal
他还说什么男子汉要有义气
I heard him fart
我听他在放屁
Really…
真是的…
Fifty million won…
五千万韩元…
Brothers are very unhappy
兄弟们都很不爽
Now there is a valid reason
现在也有正当的理由了
The time has come, right?
时机已经成熟了吧
Just now
就是现在
Douxue, let’s get rid of Guangzhuo.
斗学 把光卓除掉吧
I can be the first one
我可以冲第一个
The time has indeed come
时机确实已经成熟了
Brother Guangzhuo was not like that before...
光卓大哥以前不是那样的…
It's not all because of damn greed
还不都是因为该死的贪念
Douxue also said
斗学也说过
He will divide us when there is only petty profit
只有蝇头小利时 他会分我们
But when there is gold and silver, he will definitely keep it to himself
但有金银财宝时 他绝对会独吞
So…
所以…
Are you about to take action?
要行动了吗
No
不行
Why not?
为什么还不行
Because I have the final say
因为我说了算
Hello Douxue
喂 斗学
Douxue
斗学
Big brother…
大哥…
(Diagnosis Choi Young-sik) non-obstructive azoospermia
(诊断书 崔英植) 非阻塞型无精症
The date of diagnosis was three months before the wedding
诊断日期是婚礼前的三个月
sorry
抱歉
If only I had known earlier
要是我早点知道的话
I won’t let Mr. Tetsuo suffer like that.
就不会让哲雄公子受那种苦了
I'm really sorry
真的非常抱歉
The so-called life is really wonderful.
所谓的人生还真是妙不可言
I really almost...
我真的差点就…
Almost...
差点就…
(Violent clashes occurred at the Mingdangdong demolition site)
(名堂洞拆迁现场发生暴力冲突)
There's something I'm curious about
有件事我很好奇
You haven't seen Huang Cichang for a long time, right?
你们也很久没看到黄次长了吧
Right
对啊
Chief Huang, isn't he coming now?
黄次长他现在不来了吗
It seems so
看来是这样
Without the backer of Chief Huang,
要是没有黄次长这个靠山
My husband will become isolated and helpless.
我先生就会变得孤立无援了
That is to say
就是说啊
Are we It’s time to find another place to party.
我们是不是 也该找其他地方聚会了
Oh my god, Chief Huang, welcome.
天啊 黄次长 欢迎光临
We are about to break up the meeting
我们正要散会了呢
Everyone, let's go
各位 走吧
See you next time Luo
下次见罗
What a superficial woman
真是肤浅的女人
She doesn’t even know her husband I get scolded by my superior every day
她都不知道自己的先生 每天都被长官臭骂
Be careful if others overhear you
小心被别人听到了
So what if I hear it
听到又怎样
According to her husband's performance I wouldn't be surprised if I get fired one day
依她先生的表现 就算哪天被炒鱿鱼我也不意外
Have you been busy recently?
你最近很忙吗
Would you like a cup of coffee?
要来杯咖啡吗
No need
不必了
Do you want to drink?
那要喝酒吗
No, that's not what I need
不用 我需要的不是这些
No matter how busy I am at work
就算工作再怎么忙
How can you skip dinner?
怎么能不吃晚餐呢
People think we eat delicacies from mountains and seas every day
人们都以为我们每天吃山珍海味
But in fact, we often don’t have time to eat
但其实我们常常没时间吃饭
As the saying goes, all it takes is one missed meal
俗话说只要错过一餐
No matter how much you eat, you can't make up for it.
无论再怎么吃都补不回来
So please eat on time
所以请你按时吃饭吧
Ruzhen, please help me cook.
汝珍你帮我做饭吧
It's not too late to start now
现在开始也为时不晚
Is that why you came to us so late?
所以你才那么晚来找我们吗
What else should I do?
不然怎么办
My mother even called me and asked me to spend the night outside.
我妈都打电话叫我在外面过夜了
I don’t know any relatives in Seoul
我在首尔又没有认识的亲戚
You want me, a weak woman, to stay in a hotel Very scary
要我一个弱女子去旅馆投宿 很可怕耶
Yes, it's a good bet you came to us
是啊 好险你有来找我们
It seems she has a man
看来她是有男人了
That must be it
一定是这样啦
Otherwise, why would I suddenly kick you out?
不然怎么会突然把你赶出来呢
What do you mean by that?
你说那什么不像话的
What's wrong?
哪里不像话了
Anyway, her husband is gone. What does it matter?
反正她老公不在了 有什么关系
Do you want to be like the women of the Joseon Dynasty? Be a widow until death?
难道要跟朝鲜时代的女人一样 守寡到死吗
I will go to Zhenyu's room to sleep
我会去贞玉的房间睡
You guys should go to sleep too
你们也快睡吧
That room is very cold
那间房很冷耶
She actually has a man
她竟然有男人了
What's going on?
这是怎么回事啊
Oh my god, I'm so shy...
天啊 真害羞…
OMG…
天啊…
So shy
好害羞喔
These are the pajamas Tetsuo wore before I don't know if it looks good on you.
这是哲雄之前穿的睡衣 不知道你穿起来合不合身
If you tell me beforehand I can buy your pajamas first
如果你事先跟我说一声 我就能先买好你的睡衣
Good night then
那么晚安了
You know it will fit you even without wearing it.
不用穿也知道一定合身
After all, it's my son's pajamas
毕竟是我儿子的睡衣
Brother Loyalty
忠诚哥
live with me
和我住在一起吧
Three meals a day with you
一日三餐和你
Now I don’t want to miss it anymore
如今我都再也不想错过了
What you have suffered over the years
这些年来你受过的苦
I will make it up to you
我都会补偿你
Brother Loyalty, I am satisfied now.
忠诚哥 现在这样我就满足了
Brother Zhongzhong, thank you
忠诚哥 谢谢你
I will find a chance to tell Tetsuo
我会找机会跟哲雄说的
Tell him about our relationship
告诉他我们的关系
You see what I mean?
你明白我的意思了吧
I know you said it many times
我知道 你说过很多次了
if someone asks me
如果有人问我
I would say the lady's son I delivered the baby myself
我会说夫人的儿子 是我亲手接生的
Don't worry
你别担心啦
(Diagnosis Choi Young-sik) Is it non-obstructive azoospermia?
(诊断书 崔英植) 非阻塞型无精症吗
(Dean Luo Yaoquan) Dean, please
(罗药权院长) 院长 拜托您了
Because of the child’s father’s political leanings
因为孩子他爸的政治倾向
may affect His appointment as prosecutor
可能会影响到 他的检察官任用问题
(Dean Luo Yaoquan)
(罗药权院长)
Dean, please help me
院长 请您帮帮我
I only have that son left now
我现在只剩那个儿子
If something goes wrong with him
要是他出什么差错
I…
我…
I won't survive, Dean.
我会活不下去的 院长
please help me
请您帮帮我
I will never forget this kindness
我绝对不会忘记这份恩情
Keiko, you're back
庆子 你回来啦
Yes
对
How are you doing these days?
您这阵子过得好吗
Keiko, sorry
庆子 不好意思
can you go out for a moment
你可以出去一下吗
OK
好的
so
所以呢
How do you answer
你们怎么回答
I was so scared that I couldn't speak
我被吓得说不出话
It was too late, but it was so fast that my husband happened to show up.
说时迟那时快 我先生刚好出现
Just say that Tetsuo is your biological son.
就说哲雄是你们的亲生儿子了
I've heard that if you want to serve in an important organization
我听说过若要在重要的机关任职
A wealth survey will be conducted
就会进行身家调查
But the other person always makes me feel a little unusual
但对方总让我觉得有点不寻常
We are not in our hometown anymore He also came here
我们都不在老家了 他还找到这里来
And…
而且…
What's wrong?
怎么了吗
That person looks familiar
那个人看起来有点眼熟
When living in Lishui
住在丽水时
I have followed guests from Mrs. Chu's house before Passed by several times
我之前曾跟进出夫人家的客人 擦肩而过几次
That person looked very similar to the guest at that time
那个人跟当时的客人很像
How is it possible
怎么可能
You must have read it wrong
一定是你看错了
I feel like that person seems to know something Just came to the door
我觉得那个人好像是知道些什么 才找上门的
It made me break out in a cold sweat
害我吓出一身冷汗
How is it possible
怎么可能
Is there something he should know?
他应该要知道什么吗
what
什么
Please completely forget the wrong ideas in your mind
请彻底忘掉你们脑中错误的想法
Tetsuo is my son
哲雄是我儿子
Got it?
知道了吗
I also hope to forget
我也希望可以忘掉
But it's not something I can control
但这也不是我能控制的
you really are...
你真的是…
sorry
抱歉
I will talk to her well when I go back
我回去会好好说她的
Let's go first
我们先走了
Get up quickly
快起来
please wait a moment
请等一下
A studious mother
斗学的妈
Could you please help me with something?
能麻烦你帮我做事吗
what
什么
Our family has caused a lot of trouble for you before.
我们家先前替你们添了很多麻烦
If you come to help, you can also supplement the family income.
你来帮忙 也能顺便贴补家用
I remember you were good at driving a cultivator, right?
我记得你很会驾驶耕耘机吧
Life is really full of surprises
人生还真是无奇不有
The person who always avoids me
总是对我避之唯恐不及的人
She actually asked me to do something for her
竟然要我帮她做事
I'm already this age He actually asked me to take a driver's license test
我都这把年纪了 竟然叫我去考驾照
It's so ridiculous
真是太荒唐了
Don't dwell on it, just help.
不要碎碎念 帮忙就对了
No matter how I think about it, I feel She was afraid that I would reveal Tetsuo's life experience.
我怎么想都觉得 她是怕我把哲雄的身世说出去
She just wants me to stay by her side to monitor me
才希望我待在她身边 以便监视我
Why can’t you let go of Tetsuo now?
你怎么现在还放不下哲雄
How could I forget him
我怎么可能忘得了他
If there was an eraser in the world that could erase memories Please bring it to me
世上要是有能抹去记忆的橡皮擦 麻烦你拿来给我
You are really...
你这个人真的是…
So you don't help me
所以你不帮忙罗
Of course I want to help
当然要帮忙
This way you can see it often My son who became a prosecutor
这样还能常常看到 我那当上检察官的儿子
Try saying that again
你再说一次这种话试试看
Then I will really...
到时我就真的…
I know... I just won't say it...
知道啦… 我不说就是了…
Really
真是的
What's so hard about driving?
开车有什么难的
(Prosecutor Choi Cheol-woong)
(崔哲雄检察官)
Come and see the urban renewal areas
来 你看都市更新的地区
Now these three places are left
现在剩下这三个地方
I think it would be best if everyone can buy it
我觉得如果都能买下是最好的
If you have to choose
如果要做选择的话
Just buy it here...
就买这边…
(Boss of Star Industrial, Byun Hak-soo)
(明星兴业 卞学洙老板)
next time work
下一次作业时
Just like this Jisoo you...
就像这样 吉洙你…
(Violent clashes occurred at the Mingdangdong demolition site Mobilization of gangsters leads to violent clashes)
(名堂洞拆迁现场发生暴力冲突 流氓动员导致暴力冲突)
(Gangster mobilization leads to violent clashes Violent suppression of residents at Mingdangdong demolition site)
(流氓动员导致暴力冲突 名堂洞拆迁现场暴力镇压居民)
Choi Cheol-woong, congratulations on your appointment as prosecutor.
崔哲雄 恭喜你被任用为检察官
I originally planned to keep my distance from you.
我本来打算跟你保持距离的
But you are now a prosecutor
但你都当上检察官了
If I didn't come to say congratulations You will definitely be angry with me forever
要是我不来道贺 你一定会气我一辈子
That's why I made up my mind to come see you
所以我才下定决心来见你
That's right
没错
I was planning to do it if you didn't show up
我本来打算要是你不出现
I'm going to sue you
我就要起诉你的
Shero
谢罗
I heard a lawyer I know say
我听认识的律师说
I was fined just for parking illegally on the red line. It would be difficult to become a prosecutor
光是在红线违规停车被处罚金 就很难当上检察官了
So honestly I thought you had no chance
所以老实说 我本来以为你没机会了
You are truly amazing…
你真的很了不起…
If you miss it because of the fine It's a pity that I'm such a talented person.
要是因为那点罚金就错过 我这个人才 有点可惜吧
The senior management of our unit is very discerning, right?
我们单位高层很有眼光吧
Can boast enough
有够会自吹自擂
You are a disease
你这是一种病
Do you and Brother Douxue meet often?
你跟斗学哥常常见面吗
That silly boy
那个傻小子喔
I moved again a while ago
前阵子又搬家了
i'm looking for him
我正在找他
He will come later
他待会就会来
I called him
我叫他来了
Really?
真的吗
You are very clever at times like this
你这种时候特别机灵
Does he know I'm here too?
他知道我也在这里吗
I told him
我有跟他说
Will he do it because I'm here? If you want to hide from me, you won’t come.
他会不会因为我在这里 想要躲我 就不来啦
He will definitely come
他一定会来的
He is better than anyone They all still want me to become a prosecutor.
他比任何人 都还希望我当上检察官
And I have something important to tell him.
而且我有重要的事要跟他说
What's going on
什么事
Promise me first that you won't be angry
先答应我你不会生气
OK I'm not angry
好 我不生气
what's going on
是什么事
The prosecutor who came in at the same time as me Sitting in the box next to
和我同期进来的检察官 坐在旁边的包厢
Because we received a report
因为我们接到检举了
(Violent clashes occurred at the Mingdangdong demolition site)
(名堂洞拆迁现场发生暴力冲突)
Violent conflict in Mingdangdong Doggeng
名堂洞都更的暴力冲突
The identities of the participants are still being investigated.
目前还在调查参与者身分
But I was also shocked when I saw these photos
但我看到这些照片也吓了一跳
"Should I say something to him?"
"是否该跟他说些什么"
"When I'm indecisive"
"在我犹豫不决时"
(live acoustic guitar singing) "He left"
(木吉他现场演唱) "他便离开了"
"I gave my heart" Hello Prosecutor Choi, congratulations.
"我献上了我的心" 喂 崔检察官 恭喜你
"I shed tears for him"
"为他掉了眼泪"
How are you doing lately?
你最近过得好吗
"I will also dream..." You stinky gangster
"也将梦想…" 你这个臭流氓
You moved behind my back Is this just for doing this?
你背着我搬家 就是为了做这种事吗
Is that you in the photo?
照片中的人是你吧
Yes
对
Where did these photos come from?
这些照片是哪来的
Sent by people
民众寄来的
This is what the underworld does
这就是黑道在做的工作
If you want to teach me a lesson, just leave.
你如果想教训我就走吧
Hello Cui Zhexiong
喂 崔哲雄
Why don't we just arrest him and imprison him?
直接把他抓去关不就得了
Why are you showing me these photos?
为什么要把这些照片拿给我看
You really haven't changed at all...
你还真是一点都没变…
Tetsuo, use your clever head Use it in the right place
哲雄 把你那聪明的脑袋 用在对的地方吧
Dingchen…
定辰…
Wait a minute...
等一下…
Every time the three of us meet It doesn't end well
每次我们三人见面时 结局都不怎么好呢
Please don’t take photos like this again.
拜托你不要再被拍到这种照片了
That's why I asked you to be a prosecutor
这就是我叫你当检察官的原因
what do you want me to do
你想要我怎么做
If you get information like this Just help me, right?
像这样拿到情报的话 就要帮我才对吧
Do you ask the prosecutor to protect gangsters?
你叫检察官包庇流氓吗
have you forgotten
你忘了吗
I know I still owe you
我知道我还亏欠你
But it shouldn’t be repaid in this way, right?
但不应该是用这种方式偿还吧
No matter if I'm a gangster or not
不管我是不是流氓
It doesn’t matter if you are a prosecutor or not.
也不管你是不是检察官
You have to repay the debt you owe me Until I yell stop
你都得偿还亏欠我的债 直到我喊停为止
I get it…
我知道了…
But don’t involve Dingchen
但是你别把定辰牵扯进来
Don't let her become unhappy because of you
别让她因为你而变得不幸
I never involved her
我从没把她牵扯进来
That's why I moved
所以我才会搬家
Also
还有
Same for you
你也一样
I know you are afraid that Dingchen will be taken away by me
我知道你害怕定辰被我抢走
why
为什么
Because you are a sore loser
因为你是个输不起的家伙
But you figure it out
但你搞清楚
This is not love, but possessiveness
这不是爱 而是占有欲
Brat
臭小子
Coming...
来了…
Brother, who is coming?
大哥 是谁要来啊
Don't know
不知道
Brother, please come in
大哥请进
Thank you for your hard work, Boss Lian.
廉老板 辛苦你了
thank you
谢谢
As long as you can do your part for the country
只要能为国家尽一份力
We are always ready to be dispatched
我们随时恭候差遣
Hello…
喂…
Say hello
打声招呼吧
This is Team Leader Wu, our minister’s confidant.
这位是我们部长的亲信吴组长
He is the person with real power in our unit
是我们单位握有实权的人
You know what I mean
你懂我的意思吧
Team leader Wu said he wants to see you So we came together
吴组长说想见你 所以就一起来了
My name is Lian Guangzhuo. Please give me some advice.
我叫廉光卓 请多指教
My surname is Wu
敝姓吴
This is the case The brother in charge of on-site command
这是这次案子 负责现场指挥的兄弟
He and I are like sworn brothers in Taoyuan Guan Yu and Zhang Fei
他跟我就像桃园结义的 关羽和张飞
We are brothers
我们是拜把兄弟
Come and say hello
来 打声招呼
My name is Li Douxue
我叫李斗学
Have we met before?
我们之前见过面吧
Thank you for your hard work
辛苦你了
Although there was a bit of bloodshed
虽然爆发了一点流血冲突
But you handled things well
但你把事情处理得很好
thank you for your compliment
谢谢您的称赞
Boss Lian, come here
廉老板 你来一下
yes
是的
It is said that apartment buildings will be built in more areas in the future.
话说之后都更地区要盖公寓大厦
Yes
是
I'll contract out the window frames for the apartment to you.
公寓的窗框就发包给你吧
what
什么
Won't you give me the right to move in?
不给我入住权吗
Right of occupancy?
入住权吗
Are you still not satisfied with this?
这样你还不满意喔
don't you know How much can you earn from window frames alone?
难道你不知道 光是窗框就能赚多少了吗
That's not what I meant
我不是这个意思
Section Chief Thank you
科长 谢谢您
Why are you still dumbfounded? Let the lady come in quickly.
你还楞着干嘛 快让小姐进来
Section Chief
科长
I found one for you A special lady comes in
我为您找了一个 特别的小姐进来
Really?
是吗
I'm looking forward to it
我很期待喔
Stay tuned
敬请期待
Yeon Joo
妍珠
boss
老板
Just promise me once Wait a minute...
答应我一次就好 等一下…
This is my first time asking you to do this
我第一次这样拜托你
I don't want
我不要
Yeonjoo, I'm sorry
妍珠 对不起啦
I really don't want to go in
我真的不想进去
Yeon Joo, please save me just once.
妍珠 拜托你救我一次就好
ok
好吗
Boss, please let me go
老板 拜托您放过我
Don't you know very well that I hate this kind of thing the most?
您不是很清楚我最痛恨这种事吗
Of course I know...
我当然清楚…
So just once is enough
所以说 一次就好
Yanzhu, please let me ask you for help
妍珠 算我拜托你
Today’s guest is a high-ranking guest
今天来的客人位高权重
Go get acquainted It will also be very helpful to you
去认识一下 对你也会很有帮助的
That's what you insist on I won’t be an actor anymore
您坚持要这样的话 我就不做演员了
Hello…
喂…
Hey, I've been begging you so hard
喂 我都那么苦苦哀求你了
Do you really want to do this to me? Are you sure?
你真的要这样对我吗 你确定吗
Boss, I just want to ask you not to do this to me.
老板 我才要拜托您别这样对我
You really want to drink wine as a penalty instead of eating the toast...
你真的是敬酒不吃吃罚酒…
what is this doing
这是在做什么
What are you doing?
搞什么
Why don't you let go?
你还不放手吗
Wait a minute, it hurts...
等一下 好痛…
You little bastard, let go now
你这个小混混 快点放手
This woman is really...
这女人真的是…
my neck… Hello
我的脖子… 喂
Be more respectful
放尊重一点
ok sorry
好的 抱歉
Hello…
喂…
I'm here to meet your boss
我是来跟你们老大见面的
Then please go in alone. She even said she didn't want to go in.
那请你一个人进去吧 她都说不想进去了
what
什么
Let's go
快走吧
Hello Song Yanzhu...
喂 宋妍珠…
stop
给我站住
Wait a minute...
等一下…
Why is it so noisy?
怎么这么吵
It hurts...
好痛…
Boss Yin, what are you doing before you come in?
尹老板 你还不进来在干嘛
Where is Song Yeon-joo?
宋妍珠呢
I want to ask you
我倒要问你们
This guy is the one who twisted my wrist
都是这小子扭住我的手腕
Let Song Yanzhu run away
让宋妍珠给跑了
Abominable
可恶
what
什么
Brother, sorry
大哥 抱歉
Because Song Yanzhu doesn’t want to go in But he dragged her here
因为宋妍珠不想进去 但他硬是把她拖来
Brat...
臭小子…
Don't you know how important this is?
你不知道这是多重要的场合吗
Who are you? How dare you decide her stay or go without permission?
你算老几 竟敢擅自决定她的去留
Brother, be gentle with your feet.
大哥 脚下留情吧
how are you
你是怎样
Won't you get out of the way?
不让开吗
Big brother
大哥
Impolite brat
没礼貌的臭小子
Is this how you manage your younger brother?
你是这样管理小弟的吗
Catch Song Yanzhu quickly
快把宋妍珠抓回来
Go and get it back...
快去抓回来…
Big brother
大哥
It's my fault. Hit me.
是我的错 您打我吧
What are you guys like?
你们这群家伙是怎样
Hello Li Douxue
喂 李斗学
Now you teach him a lesson in front of me
你现在当着我的面好好教训他
Brat, hurry up
臭小子 快点
Good job
好好工作啦
are you kidding
你在开玩笑吗
This is a lesson, you brat.
这样才是教训 臭小子
Get up...
给我起来…
Hurry up and teach him a lesson
快点教训他
You boy
你这小子
What do you want now?
现在是想怎样
Brat
臭小子
enough
够了
Yeon Joo
妍珠
Boss Yin, bring her in quickly
尹老板 快带她进来
I'll settle the score with you later
我之后再找你们算帐
Do you know?
知道了没
Boss Yin, hurry up
尹老板 快点
Yanzhu, come here quickly...
妍珠 快过来…
Hello, I am movie star Song Yeon-joo.
你们好 我是电影明星宋妍珠
I love watching your movies
我很爱看你演的电影
I have read almost all of your works
你的作品我几乎都看过了
Of course, while my wife is away
当然是趁我老婆不在时
Sirs, please take a look
各位长官请看
She is both beautiful and good at acting
她既漂亮 演技又好
It's just impeccable.
简直无可挑剔吧
Thanks for the compliment
谢谢称赞
Let's listen to Miss Song Yeon-joo sing a song
我们听宋妍珠小姐唱首歌
Come on, everyone applaud
来 大家鼓掌
Thank you for your compliments
谢谢各位赏脸
But I'm not going to sing
但我不打算唱歌
I’m not going to pour wine for you either.
也不打算帮各位倒酒
Song Yanzhu, what’s wrong with you?
宋妍珠 你这是怎么了
I plan not to be Song Yeon-joo anymore
我打算不当宋妍珠了
What you like Is it the movie star Song Yeon-joo?
各位喜欢的 是电影明星宋妍珠吧
My real name is Park Jung Mi
我的本名是朴正美
from this moment on
从现在这一刻起
I'm not a movie actor, and I'm not Song Yeon-joo either.
我不是电影演员 也不是宋妍珠
I want to live as Park Jung Mi
我要以朴正美的身分生活
Then I can go now
那我现在可以走了吧
-what is she talking about -What's going on?
-她在说什么 -怎么回事
What are you doing?
搞什么
Sorry, I took her away first.
不好意思 我先带她走了
Sorry, what should I do now?
抱歉 这下该怎么办呢
Would you like a glass of soju with the omelette?
要不要来杯烧酒配煎鸡蛋卷
Your tone of voice is too indifferent, right?
你的语气也太没大没小了吧
Don't look at me like this. I have a baby face.
别看我这样 我是娃娃脸
I don't drink with actors
我不跟演员喝酒
I just decided not to do it
我刚刚已经决定不干了
I don't drink with my sister
我不跟姊姊喝酒
Egg hot compress is not effective for bruises
瘀青用鸡蛋热敷没效
Apply this
敷这个吧
Apply ice once or twice and it won't hurt anymore
再冰敷个一两次就不会痛了
If the bruise spreads, apply warm compresses with a towel
如果瘀青散开 就用毛巾热敷
It will get better soon
很快就会好转
Are you a gangster too? You know so much
你也是小混混吗 懂得真多
I do know a lot
我确实懂得不少
The little bastard can at least fight back.
小混混至少还可以还手
But in this circle you can only get beaten
但在这个圈子只能挨揍
If you go to the hospital, the news will spread
如果去医院 消息就会传出去
Over time I became an expert on bruises
久而久之我就变成了瘀青专家
If you're curious about other types of wounds Just ask me how to deal with it
如果你好奇其他种类的伤口 该怎么处理 就尽管问我
What if you were hit with a stick and broke a bone?
如果被棍棒打到骨折呢
What's wrong
怎么了
Don’t you know this?
这你就不知道了吗
Of course you have to go to the hospital, idiot
那当然要去医院啊 白痴
You are simply a psychopath
你简直是个神经病耶
really sorry
真的很抱歉
please forgive me
请原谅我
It doesn’t matter…
没关系…
I didn't come here to drink in the first place.
我本来就不是来喝酒的
I came here because I have something to discuss with Boss Lian.
我是有事要和廉老板商量才来的
So you don’t have to pay too much attention
所以你不用太在意
Is there anything I can do to help?
有什么我帮得上忙的地方
I will definitely try my best to help
我一定会尽力帮忙
Only gives you the exclusive right to sell the window frame
只给你窗框的独卖权
You must be dissatisfied
你一定不满意吧
How is it possible
怎么可能
Don’t just be responsible for driving away the demolition households
别只是负责赶走拆迁户
How about participating directly in the program?
直接参与计划怎么样
What? Directly involved?
什么 直接参与吗
Of course I want to
我当然很想
But we haven’t been able to raise that much money yet.
但目前还筹措不到那么多资金
Boss Lian only needs to prepare 20% of the funds.
廉老板只要准备20%的资金就好
We can prepare the rest
剩余的我们可以负责准备
We will also personally allocate the land to be developed
要开发的土地我们也会亲自分配
100% certain
百分百可以确定
This is not just in Seoul
这不仅是在首尔
It is a metropolitan plan that covers the entire metropolitan area.
是覆盖了整个首都圈的都更计划
Of course the profits are astronomical
利润当然也是天文数字
But I have a condition
但我有个条件
You say it
您说吧
first
首先
We hold 70% of the shares and you hold 30%
股分我们占七成 您占三成
We will give you 10% more shares
我们会多给您一成的股分
because of money laundering and tax expenses
是因为洗钱和税金方面的支出
All included in Boss Lian’s shares
都包含在廉老板的股分里
Got it
知道了
Second, even in front of King Yama
第二 就算在阎罗王面前
I can't even tell you about our cooperative relationship.
也不能说出我们的合作关系
If this is violated
如果违反了这一点
The consequences may be disastrous
后果可能会不堪设想
I swear
我发誓
I will definitely be loyal to you
我一定会效忠您
And…
还有…
I have one more thing to ask you
我还有一件事情想拜托你
Please tell me
请说吧
Please walk slowly
请慢走
Please walk carefully and slowly
请小心慢走
Douxue
斗学
Did I go a little too far just now?
我刚才是不是有点过分
It's okay, brother
没关系 大哥
But why does he come to you?
不过他来找您有什么事
nothing
没什么
He just came to please me
他只是来拜托我
Continue to help him like you are doing now
以后继续像现在这样帮他
Really
真是的
So boring
真无趣
That's right
就是啊
I would have done it even if he didn't say it
他不说我也会那么做
Hello Douxue
喂 斗学
Don't be angry
你别生气了
After all I am the boss
毕竟我是老板
But he was embarrassed in front of the guests
却在客人面前丢脸
I'm too excited
是我太激动了
Right
对了
This…
这个…
You take it and treat your little brothers to delicious food.
你拿去请小弟们吃好吃的
relax
放松一下心情
Thank you bro
谢谢大哥
No. Let’s get off work.
不会 大家下班吧
Please walk slowly, brother
请慢走 大哥
So crowded
好挤
where
在哪里
here
在这里
These funds alone are absolutely not enough
只有这些资金绝对不够
No matter how hard I think, I can't think of a way
怎么想也想不到办法
drink
喝吧
Cow, you can eat it from head to tail
牛啊 从头到尾巴都能吃
Not even willing to throw away the internal organs A nation that cooks and eats
连内脏都舍不得丢 还煮来吃的民族
It's probably just us
大概就只有我们了
We often come here to eat the offal soup
我们很常来吃这家店的内脏汤
Yes
是啊
The eldest brother also said that we should be together for the rest of our lives. Brothers who show their sincerity to each other
大哥还说我们要当一辈子 肝胆相照的兄弟
Yes
是啊
That's why I came to see you again
所以我才又来找你
Do you remember what I said?
你记得我说过的话吧
The person who will inherit my country from now on
以后要继承我江山的人
This is not Li Douxue who became a monk halfway.
不是半路出家的李斗学
It’s you who worked hard with me when I was young
而是年轻时跟我一起打拚的你
you know tiger
你知道老虎
Will push his child off the cliff
会把自己的孩子推下悬崖
Then only raise children who can crawl back.
然后只抚养爬得回来的孩子吧
you are like that
你就是那样
And that guy Douxue
还有斗学那家伙
It has nothing to do with eating offal soup with me.
不是能跟我吃内脏汤的关系
Come
来
Thank you for your hard work
辛苦你了
We hold 70% of the shares and you hold 30%
股分我们占七成 您占三成
We will give you 10% more shares
我们会多给您一成的股分
because of money laundering and tax expenses
是因为洗钱和税金方面的支出
All included in Boss Lian’s shares
都包含在廉老板的股分里
I know
我知道了
Second, even in front of King Yama
第二 就算在阎罗王面前
I can't even tell you about our cooperative relationship.
也不能说出我们的合作关系
If this is violated
如果违反了这一点
The consequences may be disastrous
后果可能会不堪设想
Because we need to know what big brother is doing
因为我们得知道大哥在搞什么鬼
If there is a 30% stake in the development company
如果有开发公司三成的股份
How much money can you make
能赚多少钱
Although only 30%
虽然只有三成
But development projects cost several billions Billions of dollars
但开发案都是几十亿来 几十亿去的
Of course the income is at the level of a large company
收入当然是大企业的水准
We…
我们…
Eat this business
吞掉这笔生意吧
This is a chance for brother
这是给大哥的机会
They will get rid of big brother Leave the work to us?
他们会甩掉大哥 把工作交给我们吗
That's right
就是啊
It doesn't matter to them who they do it for
对他们来说给谁做不重要
What matters is how good that person is
重要的是那个人的能力有多出色
Are you saying this is the level of a big company?
你不是说这是大企业的水准
Let's just vote
我们干脆大干一票
Get out of this miserable situation
摆脱悲惨的现况吧
How long are we going to live like this?
我们要这样活到什么时候
You should have guessed the other party’s identity, right?
你应该也猜到对方的身分了吧
So what?
所以呢 那又怎么样
You should consider carefully
你要谨慎地考虑
Those people live in a different world than us
那些人跟我们活在不同的世界
They can…
他们可以…
Killing us without anyone noticing
神不知鬼不觉地杀了我们
Kill someone?
杀人吗
Kill us?
杀我们吗
Which organization is it?
是哪个组织
Haven't you seen it before?
你不是也见过
South Korea's CIA
韩国的中情局
I'm so scared
我好害怕
You can quit if you're scared
害怕的话你可以退出
Do you want to grab it?
要抢过来吗
I heard you are selling drugs recently
听说你最近在卖毒品
what
什么
how do you know
您怎么知道
sorry
对不起
Because money is tight recently So I sold it temporarily
因为最近手头比较紧 所以暂时卖了一下
I know you don't like it
我知道您不喜欢
I can stop doing it now...
我可以现在就不做…
It doesn’t matter…
没关系…
When money is tight What does selling drugs have to do with it?
手头很紧时 卖个毒品有什么关系
But since we have to do it Why not make it bigger
不过既然要做 为什么不做大一点
Brother help you
大哥帮你
Now working in the underworld
现在混黑道
money is power
金钱即是力量
If you want to make a name for yourself all over the country Even more so
想在全国各地闯名堂的话 更是那样
Selling drugs doesn't matter Just wait until you gain some weight and then stop selling it.
卖毒品无所谓 等你有分量了以后再不卖就好
Isn't it?
不是吗
Brother, why did you suddenly say that?
大哥 您怎么突然这么说
Yongbi
永弼
How long will you stay in the junior suite?
你要住小套房住到什么时候
Even if it's not a house with ninety-nine rooms
就算不是有九十九间房间的房子
At least rent a decent house
至少也要租一间像样的房子
Let's fart comfortably in there
在里面舒服地放个屁吧
That way…
那样…
It’s interesting for me to choose a successor.
我选接班人才有意思啊
Big brother
大哥
But suddenly it expanded
但是突然扩大规模
It would be dangerous if rumors spread
传出传闻的话会很危险
Even my eldest brother...
连大哥也…
You give it a try
你试试看吧
Just treat it like a little tiger has to face it The last hurdle
就当是小老虎要面对的 最后一道关卡
And I can't get involved in drugs. in related cases
还有我不能被卷进毒品 相关的案件里
You understand
你懂吧
I will keep it in mind, brother
我会谨记在心的 大哥
No
不行
why
为什么
Why do you always say no?
你为什么总是说不行
If you say no, can't we do it?
你说不行 我们就不能做吗
Well, I can't
嗯 不能
Am I your dog...
我是你的狗吗…
Because I'm the boss
因为我是老大
Team Leader Wu, only we can know about this.
吴组长 这件事只有我们能知道
Don’t let anyone else in the company know
不能让公司里的其他人知道
Yes
是
But how much do you know
不过您知道多少
I only know the minister and the chief of security
我只知道部长和警卫室长
Don't fund them with company funds
别用公司的资金资助他们
Help them get a bank loan
帮他们去银行贷款
Can't leave them with us Transaction records
不能留下他们和我们 交易过的记录
Got it
知道了
Also
还有
In addition, we retain 10% of our equity
另外保留我们10%的股权
I can't guarantee I'll still be sitting How long have you been in this position?
我无法保证我还能坐在 这个位子上多久
It’s time for Team Leader Wu to prepare to retire.
吴组长也该准备退休了
Isn't it?
不是吗
thank you
谢谢
Who told you to lie down
谁叫你躺着
Lie down for me
你给我趴好
Douxue, wait a minute
斗学啊 等等
Who allows you to call the boss by his name?
谁准你随便叫老大的名字
Operation Captain
行动队长
Lie down
趴好
Douxue, okay, stop fighting.
斗学啊 好了 别打了
Hello
喂
If you dare to steal money again
你如果敢再偷钱
I will definitely beat you to death next time
下次我一定打死你
Let's go, brother
走吧 大哥
are you okay
你没事吧
Let me go, brat
放开我 臭小子
Abominable
可恶
1 million won
100万韩元
You just stole 1 million won Was he beaten like this?
你只是偷拿了100万韩元 就被打成这样吗
And that money is not what I want to use
而且那些钱不是我要用的
I'm buying suits for the new boys.
我是为了给新进的小弟们买西装
Just took that money
才拿了那些钱
In addition to paying rent and eating
除了缴房租和吃饭
He doesn't let us spend money at all
他根本不让我们花钱
Big brother learns from Li Dou
大哥跟李斗学
Really stingy
真的太小气了
you
你们
Have you really never received any pocket money?
真的都没拿过零用钱吗
Yes, brother
对 大哥
I live with the money from my family
我都跟家里拿钱过日子
Brother, I'm still borrowing money from my friends.
大哥 我还跟朋友借钱呢
Did they keep the money for themselves?
他们把钱独吞了吗
Otherwise, how could I...
不然我怎么会…
How could I want to steal money?
我怎么会想偷钱
That guy spoke very nicely Say we are a family
那小子说得很好听 说我们是一家人
Hey, can this be called a family?
喂 这也叫一家人吗
He doesn't think we are family
他才不当我们是家人
Yongbi
永弼啊
You take me in
你收留我吧
I will help you take revenge
我会帮你报仇
You and Dou Xue have been inseparable since we were in prison.
你跟斗学从在牢里时就形影不离
How do you want me to believe you?
你要我怎么相信你
I learn from Dou
我把斗学
I took all the money from the office safe
办公室保险箱里的钱都拿来了
30 million won
三千万韩元
I could have taken the money and run away
我本来可以拿这些钱跑路的
But I came to you
但我却来找你
Because I want revenge
因为我想报仇
I seem to be able to feel your sincerity
我好像能感受到你的真心了
These are just the tip of the iceberg
这些只是冰山一角
In Lian Guangzhuo's vault
廉光卓的金库里
There is ten times more money than this
有比这多十倍的钱
I run errands for him every month So I know it very well
我每个月都会去帮他跑腿 所以很了解
Doesn’t Lian Guangzhuo dislike going to the bank?
廉光卓不是很不喜欢去银行吗
indeed
确实是
Now working in the underworld
现在混黑道
money is power
金钱就是力量
Just steal Lian Guangzhuo's treasury
只要去偷廉光卓的金库
Each of my brothers can save a few million more
小弟们每个人能多存几百万
Lian Guangzhuo and Li Douxue
廉光卓和李斗学
Let's get rid of them all in one go.
一口气解决掉他们吧
I want that too
我也很想那样
But the timing doesn't seem right
但时机点好像不太对
Hello
喂
What are you arguing about?
在吵什么
what are you going to do
你们要做什么
Don't move at all
通通都别动
I am prosecutor Choi Cheol-woong
我是检察官崔哲雄
You are Yongpil
你就是永弼啊
nice to meet you
很高兴见到你
Actually
其实
My target is not you, it’s Lian Guangzhuo
我的目标不是你 是廉光卓
You know Lian Guangzhuo
你知道廉光卓
kick you out
把你赶出去
Take Li Douxue with you
带着李斗学
Trying to find ways to strengthen his power everywhere
到处想办法壮大他的势力
Selling alcohol in a bar and laundering money is the most basic thing
在酒吧卖酒洗钱是最基本的
He also helped the company suppress the labor union.
还帮忙公司打压工会
even use violence Force residents in Tugeng area to leave
甚至动用暴力 逼都更地区的住户离开
It's really a headache
真的很让人头痛
But they don’t know what backing they have
不过他们不知道有什么靠山
It runs away as fast as a loach and is hard to catch
逃跑的速度快得像泥鳅一样难抓
now because of them
现在因为他们
The public opinion situation is very bad
舆论情况很糟糕
The government says it wants to protect citizens
政府说要保护市民
So…
所以…
We have to catch someone to scare the monkeys
我们必须抓个人来杀鸡儆猴
to calm public opinion
才能平息舆论
It has been decided from above
上头已经决定了
you can take over the organization
你可以接手组织
Then learn from Lian Guangzhuo and Li Dou Give us the criminal evidence
然后把廉光卓和李斗学的 犯罪证据交给我们
Then we can quell the dissatisfaction of the people practice patriotism
那么我们就能平息国民的不满 实践爱国
You can also take revenge He can also take over the organization smoothly
你也可以报仇 还能顺势接手组织
Kill two birds with one stone, kill two birds with one stone Isn’t it the best of both worlds?
一箭双雕 一石二鸟 不是很两全其美吗
How is it
怎么样
Do you think I will believe you?
你觉得我会相信你吗
Yongbi
永弼啊
What are we doing catching a little fish like you?
我们抓你这种小鱼做什么
Our goal is to catch big fish
我们的目标是钓大鱼
Even if your name is reported to the newspaper, no one will recognize it.
你的名字就算上报也没人认识
At least like Lian Guangzhuo To be discernible
至少要像廉光卓那样 才有辨识度
Don't look down on people
你不要瞧不起人
No one knows what will happen in the future.
以后会怎样谁也不知道
Yes
是啊
So
所以
Yongbi
永弼啊
in this world
这世上
Day and night coexist
昼夜是共存的
Can there be only flowers and plants in this world?
这世上可以只有花草吗
Have rabbits that eat grass
要有吃草的兔子
There must also be wild wolves and tigers that eat rabbits
也要有吃兔子的野狼和老虎
The organization always needs someone to accept it
组织总要有人接收
Just accept it
你就接收吧
However
不过
Don't get into big trouble and cooperate with us well
你别闯大祸 好好配合我们
OK
可以吧
Hey, drive faster
喂 开快一点
is…
是…
Did you know that during the Imjin Japanese Rebellion?
你知道壬辰倭乱时
General Yi Sun-shin refused to listen to Seonjo's words No troops were sent
李舜臣将军不听宣祖的话 没有出兵
Later I got slapped The story of joining the army in white clothes
后来挨了板子 白衣从军的故事吧
People who originally disobeyed the king’s orders It must be executed immediately
本来不服王命的人 是必须立刻处死的
But General Yi Sun-shin because of his great achievements
但李舜臣将军因为立过大功
Seonjo gave him a gold medal to avoid death
宣祖给了他免死金牌
No matter what you do wrong
无论做错任何事
He can avoid death once
他都能免死一次
A token like that
像那样的信物
This is the death-free gold medal
这就是免死金牌
This document is really hard to get
这份文件真的很难拿到
Don't go around showing off to others
你不要到处去跟人炫耀
OK, then I'll stamp it...
好 那我在上面印章…
No, I'll finish pressing the fingerprint first
不 我先按完手印
If you press your fingerprint again, this document will be Save your life
你再按手印 这份文件就能 保你一命
Everything is done
一切就搞定了
(Certificate from the Supreme Prosecutor’s Office)
(大检察厅 证明书)
You are here
你来啦
Sorry I'm late
对不起 我来晚了
It's okay. Please sit down.
没关系 请坐
Do you want to order a drink first?
要不要先点饮料
It's okay, no need
没关系 不用了
good
好
Thank you for thinking of me so much
谢谢你这么为我着想
But I'm retired
但我已经退休了
when
什么时候
yesterday
昨天
So please find another actor
所以请你找别的演员
This movie will definitely be a hit
这部电影一定会大卖
This role is also suitable for you
这个角色也很适合你
And we will definitely give you dividends
还有我们一定会给你分红
If…
如果…
An actress who fell in love with a gangster
是爱上流氓的女演员
Doesn't it matter?
也没关系吗
Not in a movie, but in real life
不是在电影里 是在现实生活中
I'm such a madman
我真是个疯子
Do you remember the last time you came to the filming set? Pick up my gangster
你记得上次来拍摄现场 接我的流氓吧
Yes
是
i like him very much
我很喜欢他
I want to date him
我要跟他交往
am i crazy
我是不是疯了
Thank you for coming to your appointment today
今天谢谢你前来赴约
Then I'll leave first
那我先走了
But you are really crazy
不过你真的疯了
Be careful not to choke. Eat slowly.
小心别噎到 吃慢一点
I have to finish eating quickly
我得快点吃完
Go back to work on the case
回去处理案子
Don't you have something important to tell me?
你不是有重要的事情要跟我说
do you have a girlfriend
你有没有女朋友
I heard other prosecutors
我听说其他检察官们
When I was in training school, I would be chased by girls.
在研修院时就会被女生倒追
Did you call me back out of curiosity?
你是好奇这个才叫我回来的吗
How
怎么
Are you worried that your son won't get a wife?
你担心你儿子娶不到老婆吗
not like that
不是那样
that's why
那是为什么
If you want to get married
你如果要结婚的话
There will be one less officiant
会少一个主婚人
Forget it
算了
Let’s talk about it later
之后再说吧
do you want coffee
你要喝咖啡吗
Mom, you have a boyfriend
妈 你交男朋友啦
No
不是啦
I was right, right?
被我说中了吧
Actually…
其实…
That's great. That's great.
太好了 真是太好了
do you really think so
你真的这么想吗
Of course
当然
My mother is so young and beautiful
我妈妈这么年轻 漂亮
I have to stay alone in an empty house for the rest of my life Is this true?
下半辈子却要独守空房 这像话吗
I originally thought that if you didn't have a boyfriend
我本来还想你如果不交男朋友
I want to introduce you to someone
我要帮你介绍对象的
so good
真是太好了
Tetsuo
哲雄
Why, are you worried that I will object?
怎么 你担心我会反对吗
Is it because of dad?
是因为爸爸吗
Didn’t dad have…
爸爸不是有…
Will my son help him pass on the incense of the Cui family?
我这儿子帮他传承崔家的香火吗
However
不过
what does that person do
那个人是做什么的
where did you meet How did we know each other?
你们是在哪里认识 怎么认识的
he is a good man
他是个好人
I'll arrange to meet you later
我之后再安排你们见面
Really exciting
真令人期待
My mother actually started falling in love
我妈竟然开始谈恋爱了
You are much better than me
你比我厉害多了
very cold
很冷
You go in quickly
你快进去吧
You go back I'm leaving
你回去吧 我走了
(Terrible outsider team)
(可怕的外人球团)
The cheers from the audience came from the baseball stadium
棒球场内传来了观众的欢呼声
Hello Dingchen
喂 定辰
If you convince Director Lee Chang-ho
你如果说服了李长浩导演
You must let me sing a movie soundtrack
一定要让我唱一首电影配乐
If you don't let me sing
你如果不让我唱
I'll pack my bags and go back to Lishui
我就收拾行李回丽水
You'd better go back now
你还是现在就回去吧
It's so late. Who is it?
这么晚了 是谁啊
He came to congratulate me and said I could win the game today It’s already amazing
他来恭喜我说今天能赢得比赛 就已经很了不起了
Tetsuo
哲雄
How is it
怎么样
Would you like grilled pork belly with soju?
要吃烤五花肉配烧酒吗
Hello Dingchen
喂 定辰
why did you come
你怎么会来
You're here to celebrate your mom's boyfriend.
你是来庆祝你妈妈交男朋友的
Then you should drink it with your mother Why come here to celebrate?
那你应该跟你妈妈喝 为什么跑来这里庆祝
Are you unhappy that my mother has a boyfriend?
我妈交男朋友 你不开心吗
No
没有
It's not like you don't know her Can't you help her celebrate?
你又不是不认识她 不能帮她庆祝一下吗
Yes, of course I can help her celebrate
可以 我当然可以帮她庆祝
I just don't know Is this something I can help her celebrate?
我只是不知道 这是不是我能帮她庆祝的事
Sincere congratulations to your mother Tetsuo
真心地恭喜你妈妈 哲雄
Tetsuo, you are so handsome
哲雄 你真的好帅
How many men in the world would congratulate their mother on her remarriage?
世上有多少男人会恭喜妈妈再婚
Tetsuo
哲雄
i wrote a song
我写了一首歌
Do you want to listen to it?
你要听听看吗
good
好
"Things of the past"
"过去的事"
"Even if I try hard to remember, I will turn around."
"即使努力回想 转身"
"There will still be sad eyes"
"还是会流露出悲伤的眼神"
What a fool
真像个傻瓜
"Sader than separation"
"比离别更悲伤"
"The words wish me happiness"
"愿我幸福的这句话"
"Like stars shining in the night sky"
"像夜空中闪耀的星光"
"On your pupils"
"在你的瞳孔上"
The more I listen to this song, the more it sounds like it
这首歌越听越像
Singing about my state of mind
在唱我的心境呢
Really?
是吗
"Tears flow emptyly"
"泪水空虚地流下"
Those stinky dogs
那些臭狗
What happened to them
它们是怎么了
Brother, leave it to me to solve it
大哥交给我来解决
As for fighting studies
至于斗学
It's your responsibility to stop him
就由你负责拦住他
Never fail
绝对不能失败
If Douxue comes to help big brother Things are going to get tricky
斗学如果来帮大哥 状况会变得很棘手
What's wrong
怎么了
who are you
你们是什么人
Wait
等等
Big brother…
大哥…
What's wrong? What's wrong?
怎么了 怎么了
Brother, please take the secret passage and escape.
大哥 您快走密道逃跑吧
these bastards
这些混蛋
where has he gone
他去哪里了
Who?
谁啊
You are here
您来啦
who are you
你是谁
It's Yongpil
是永弼啊
You came just in time
你来得正好
Sure enough, you are the only one I can rely on
果然只有你靠得住
They were sent by Douxue, right?
是斗学派人来的吧
I knew he would be like this
我就知道他会这样
But Yongpil
不过永弼啊
how do you know i'm here
你怎么知道我在这里
That's right. How would I know?
就是啊 我怎么会知道呢
Yongbi
永弼
Although the sneak attack was successful
虽然偷袭成功
But he kept resisting
但他一直反抗
It's a bit laborious
有点费力呢
Thank you for your hard work
辛苦了
Big Brother, your favorite Douxue is here
大哥 你最喜欢的斗学来了
"Can I come back to you again?"
"我能再回到你身边吗"
"trembling eyes"
"颤抖的眼神"
"Looks more sad"
"显得更加哀戚"
"My heart is swaying in the desolate sky"
"我的心在荒凉的天空中飘摇"
"Your name is deeply etched in my heart"
"你的名字 深深刻在我心上"
(Preview of next episode)
(下集预告)
Prosecutor Choi might have a chance Can you handcuff me?
崔检察官说不定有机会 能替我上铐呢
I said
我说了
what was said
说了什么
break up
分手
(Wu Wanxu) This is an item confiscated from Lian Guangzhuo's house.
(吴万旭) 这是从廉光卓家没收来的物品
I found the mastermind
我找到幕后主谋了
who is
是谁
before becoming a family
在成为一家人之前
There's something I need to let you know first
有件事必须先让您知道
Dingchen
定辰
If I don’t join the underworld anymore
我如果不混黑道了
Do you want to live with me?
你愿意跟我过日子吗
you
你们
None of them are human
都不是人
Go to hell
去死吧
This is the hound you killed me price that must be paid
这是你杀了我的猎犬 必须付出的代价